Guide to the New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Committee on Arbitration, 1820s-1973
  - Subseries V.2: Case Correspondence, 1914-1930
    - Case 2182 1926-1927 (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Case 2184 1926 (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - Case 2185 1926 (Box 55, Folder 37)
    - Case 2186 1926 (Box 55, Folder 38)
    - Case 2189 1926 (Box 55, Folder 39)
    - Case 2191 1926 (Box 55, Folder 40)
    - Case 2192 1926 (Box 55, Folder 41)
    - Case 2194 1926 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Case 2195 1926 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Case 2196 1926 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Case 2198 1926 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Case 2199 1926 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Case 2201 1926 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Case 2202 1926 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Case 2203 1926 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Case 2204 1926 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Case 2206 1926 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Case 2207 1926 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Case 2208 1926 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Case 2210 1926 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Case 2211 1926 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Case 2212 1926 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Case 2214 1926 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Case 2215 1926 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Case 2216 1926 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Case 2218 1926 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Case 2222 1926 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Case 2223 1926 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Case 2226 1926 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Case 2227 1926 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Case 2228 1926 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Case 2229 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Case 2230 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Case 2231 1926 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Case 2232 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Case 2233 1926 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Case 2234 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Case 2236 1926 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Case 2237 1926 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Case 2238 1926 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - Case 2239 1926 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Case 2240 1926 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Case 2241 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Case 2242 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Case 2244 1926 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Case 2245 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Case 2248 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - Case 2250 1926-1928 (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - Case 2252 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 42)
    - Case 2253 1926 (Box 56, Folder 43)
    - Case 2254 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 44)
    - Case 2257 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 45)
    - Case 2260 1926 (Box 56, Folder 46)
    - Case 2261 1926 (Box 56, Folder 47)
    - Case 2262 1926 (Box 56, Folder 48)
    - Case 2263 1927 (Box 56, Folder 49)
    - Case 2264 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 50)
    - Case 2266 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 51)
    - Case 2267 1926 (Box 56, Folder 52)
    - Case 2268 1926 (Box 56, Folder 53)
    - Case 2270 1927 (Box 56, Folder 54)
    - Case 2271 1926-1927 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Case 2272 1927 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Case 2273 1927 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Case 2274 1927 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Case 2276 1927 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Case 2279 1927 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Case 2280 1926-1927 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Case 2281 1927 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Case 2283 1927 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Case 2284 1927-1928 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Case 2285 1927 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Case 2286 1927 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Case 2287 1927 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Case 2289 1927 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Case 2291 1927 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Case 2293 1927 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Case 2294 1927 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Case 2295 1927 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Case 2298 1927 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Case 2299 1927 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - American Trading Company v. Hartfield Telegraph Code Publishing Company, 1914 (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - Joliet Oil Tractor Company v. Francisco Perez de Alderete, 1916-1917 (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - Mann and Company v. Adolfo Hahn, 1917 (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - Orvis Brothers and Co. v. Charles Maken, 1963 (Box 325, Folder 5)
  - Subseries V.3: Chairman's Files, 1865-1967
    Subseries 3 is devoted to the records of the Chairman of the Committee on Arbitration. Correspondence files make up the bulk of the subseries and mostly derive from Committee Chairman Charles Bernheimer's tenure from 1912-1944. Both the correspondence files and the Chairman's administrative files, which make up the remainder of the subseries, illustrate Bernheimer's role in promoting arbitration at the local, national, and international levels. Materials in this subseries are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Administrative
      - Arbitration and Appeal, Committee on, 1875-1913 (Box 325, Folder 6)
      - The Arbitration Foundation, Inc., 1924-1925 (Box 325, Folder 7)
      - Arbitration Seminar--The Disputed Transaction: How Arbitration is Used in the Securities Industry, 1967 (Box 325, Folder 8)
      - Arbitration, Special Committee on--Report, 1911 (Box 325, Folder 9)
      - Bernheimer Arbitration Education Fund
        - 1924-1957 (Box 326, Folder 1)
        - Report on Publication and Distribution of Standards for Commercial Arbitration…, 1951 (Box 326, Folder 2)
        - Research Data, 1924-1945 (Box 326, Folder 3)
      - Committee
        - Annual Report, 1920-1943 (Box 326, Folder 4)
        - Case Proceedings, 1874-1878 (bound volume) (Box 463)
        - Earliest Arbitration Records of the Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York, 1779-1792 1913 (Box 326, Folder 5)
        - List of Official Arbitrators, 1920-1930 (Box 326, Folder 6)
        - Minutes, 1861-1874 (bound volume) (Box 462)
        - Minutes, 1911-1915 (bound volume) (Box 464)
        - Minutes, 1916-1922 (Box 326, Folder 7)
        - Report, 1915-1949 (Box 326, Folder 8)
        - Requests and Inquiries, 1951-1962 (Box 326, Folder 9)
        - Rules and Regulations, 1966 (Box 326, Folder 10)
        - State Laws of Arbitration, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Court of Arbitration
        - General, 1922 (Box 326, Folder 11)
        - Laws of Arbitration, 1874-1881 (Box 326, Folder 12)
        - Publications--Advantages and Importance to Business Men, 1875 (Box 326, Folder 13)
      - History of Commercial Arbitration in New York, 1922 (Box 326, Folder 14)
      - International Commercial Arbitration, 1904-1913 (Box 326, Folder 15)
      - Publications
        - Arbitration, 1920-1961 (Box 323, Folder 1)
        - Bernheimer, Charles, 1916-1923 (Box 323, Folder 2)
        - Berheimer, Charles and Julius Henry Cohen, 1911-1927 (Box 323, Folder 3)
      - Scrapbook--Court of Arbitration, 1874-1882 (bound volume) (Box 465)
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1918-1924, (3 Folders) (Box 323, Folder 4-6)
      - Adams, R.L., College of Agriculture, U.C. Berkeley, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 1)
      - American Arbitration Association Textbook, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 2)
      - American Association of Woolen and Worsted Manufacturers, 1915-1916 (Box 113, Folder 1)
      - American Bar Association in San Francisco, 1922 (Box 113, Folder 2)
      - American Chamber of Commerce
        - Brazil, 1922 (Box 113, Folder 3)
        - Chile, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 4)
        - Cuba, 1919 (Box 113, Folder 5)
      - >American Manufacturers Export Association, 1923-1924 (Box 311, Folder 3)
      - American Washing Machine Manufacturers' Association, 1916 (Box 113, Folder 6)
      - Arbitration Decisions Referred to Outside Courts, 1919-1923 (Box 113, Folder 7)
      - Arbitration Legislation, 1922 (Box 113, Folder 8)
      - A.R. Maas Chemical Company, Inc., 1926 (Box 311, Folder 4)
      - Associated Metals and Minerals Corporation, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 5)
      - Associates Stock Exchange, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 6)
      - Association of American Wood Pulp Importers
        - 1921 (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - 1926 (Box 311, Folder 7)
      - Ayling, Robert D., 1926 (Box 311, Folder 8)
      - Bar Association of the City of Boston, 1918-1919 (Box 113, Folder 10)
      - Barron, George D., 1915 (Box 113, Folder 11)
      - Bergerault, Cremer and Randel, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 9)
      - Board of Commerce Governmental Committee, Detroit, Michigan, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 10)
      - Boston Wool Trade Association, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 11)
      - California State Arbitration Bill, 1921-1927 (Box 113, Folder 12)
      - Central Committee to Promote Commercial Arbitration in Chicago, 1918 (Box 113, Folder 13)
      - Chamberlin, Emerson--List of Official Arbitrators, 1924 (Box 323, Folder 7)
      - Chamber of Commerce
        - Boston, 1927 (Box 311, Folder 12)
        - Connecticut, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 13)
        - Buenos Aires, 1916-1920, (2 Folders) (Box 113, Folder 14-15)
        - Danbury, Connecticut, 1915 (Box 113, Folder 16)
        - International Chamber of Commerce, 1922, (2 Folders) (Box 113, Folder 17-18)
        - International Chamber of Commerce, 1922-1923, (2 Folders) (Box 113, Folder 19-20)
        - London, 1915 (Box 113, Folder 21)
        - Los Angeles, 1916-1919 (Box 113, Folder 22)
        - Los Angeles, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 1)
        - Manchester, 1920-1922 (Box 114, Folder 2)
        - Massachusetts, 1919 (Box 114, Folder 3)
        - Netherlands in New York, 1922-1925, (2 Folders) (Box 114, Folder 4-5)
        - Netherlands in New York/American Exporter, 1920-1921 (Box 114, Folder 6)
        - New Jersey State, 1922-1923 (Box 114, Folder 7)
        - Panama, 1915 (Box 114, Folder 8)
        - Penang, 1915 (Box 114, Folder 9)
        - Portland, 1915 (Box 114, Folder 10)
        - St. Louis, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 14)
        - United States of America, 1921-1923 (Box 114, Folder 11)
        - United States of America in the Argentine Republic, 1919-1920 (Box 114, Folder 12)
      - Chamber of Commerce and Industrie, Symrna, Turkey, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 15)
      - Chicago Association of Credit Men, 1919 (Box 114, Folder 13)
      - Christy, Edward H., 1927 (Box 311, Folder 16)
      - Cleary, James C., 1923-1924 (Box 311, Folder 17)
      - Cleland, Mrs. H.E., 1919 (Box 115, Folder 1)
      - Commercial Arbitration, 1924 (Box 311, Folder 18-20)
      - Committees
        - Commercial Arbitration, Special Committee on, 1910 (Box 311, Folder 21)
        - Commerce, Trade, and Commercial Law, Committee on, 1922 (Box 114, Folder 14)
        - Judiciary Congress, Committee on, 1922 (Box 114, Folder 15)
      - Conlen, William J., 1926 (Box 311, Folder 22)
      - Constitutional Convention of the State of New York, 1915 (Box 114, Folder 16)
      - Credit Association of Building Trades of New York, 1918 (Box 114, Folder 17)
      - Doolittle, H.A., Bureau of Foreign and Domestic Commerce, 1917 (Box 114, Folder 18)
      - Fact Determination--J.L. Block and Sons, 1923 (Box 311, Folder 23)
      - Federal Arbitration Bill
        - 1922-1923, (2 Folders) (Box 114, Folder 19-20)
        - 1922-1923 (Box 115, Folder 2)
      - Federal Trade Commission, 1918 (Box 115, Folder 3)
      - Flaxman Dry Goods and Notion Company, 1919 (Box 115, Folder 4)
      - Foreign Trade Financing Corporation, 1919-1921 (Box 115, Folder 5)
      - Fraser, R.S., 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 6)
      - Freeman, Charles D., 1926 (Box 311, Folder 24)
      - Freschi, J.J., 1919 (Box 115, Folder 7)
      - Fulton, Robert M., 1916 (Box 115, Folder 8)
      - Government and Merchants, 1918 (Box 115, Folder 9)
      - Grand Rapid Association of Commerce, 1915 (Box 115, Folder 10)
      - Hammitt, J.O., 1926 (Box 311, Folder 25)
      - Haskins and Sells, 1923 (Box 311, Folder 26)
      - Heywood, Johnson, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 27)
      - Hochfelder, Anna W., 1923 (Box 311, Folder 28)
      - Hodgeman Rubber Company, 1918 (Box 115, Folder 11)
      - Hoover, Herbert, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 12)
      - Huff, Truman C., 1915 (Box 115, Folder 13)
      - Jewish Court of Arbitration, 1920 (Box 115, Folder 14)
      - Jiddy, Alfredo, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 29)
      - Jones, John C., 1926 (Box 311, Folder 30)
      - Jottrand, Emile, 1919 (Box 115, Folder 15)
      - "Justice and the Poor" by Reginald H. Smith, 1919-1920 (Box 115, Folder 16)
      - Kajita, Minoru, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 31)
      - Kir, Zade, Chevki and Cie, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 32)
      - Legation of Switzerland, 1913 (Box 115, Folder 17)
      - Legislation, 1919 (Box 311, Folder 33)
      - List of Arbitration Organizations, 1916-1920 (Box 115, Folder 18)
      - Marx, Joseph E., 1926 (Box 311, Folder 34)
      - McKee, Henry S., Jr., 1920 (Box 115, Folder 19)
      - Mediation and Arbitration of Business Differences Conference, 1915 (Box 115, Folder 20)
      - Merchants Association of New York
        - 1915 (Box 115, Folder 21)
        - 1927 (Box 311, Folder 35)
      - Metropolitan Pottery Company, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 36)
      - Miller, John T., 1915 (Box 115, Folder 22)
      - Mills Bill No. 1212 1915 (Box 115, Folder 23)
      - Mount Hope Finishing Company, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 37)
      - Municipal Court of Philadelphia, 1915 (Box 115, Folder 24)
      - Nathan, A. Jerrold, 1922 (Box 115, Folder 25)
      - National Association of Hosiery and Underwear Manufacturers, 1918-1919 (Box 115, Folder 26)
      - National Association of Importers of Hides and Skins, 1927-1928 (Box 311, Folder 38)
      - National Association of Tanners, 1915 (Box 115, Folder 27)
      - National Poultry, Butter and Egg Association, 1919-1922 (Box 115, Folder 28)
      - National Wholesale Grocers Association, 1919 (Box 115, Folder 29)
      - New Jersey Arbitration Law, 1923-1924 (Box 115, Folder 30)
      - New Jersey Association of Nurserymen, 1927-1928 (Box 311, Folder 39)
      - New York Globe, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 31)
      - New York Law Journal, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 1)
      - New York Public Library, 1926 (Box 311, Folder 40)
      - New York State Society of Certified Public Accountants, 1915-1916 (Box 116, Folder 2)
      - Pan American Financial Conference, 1915 (Box 116, Folder 3)
      - Pan American Union, 1912-1919 (Box 116, Folder 4)
      - Phosphate Export Association, 1919 (Box 116, Folder 5)
      - Pratt Paper Company, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 6)
      - Protocol Scheme, 1919 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - Rapp, Steven K., 1926 (Box 311, Folder 41)
      - Real Estate Board of New York, 1923 (Box 311, Folder 42)
      - Reconstruction Commission of the State of New York, 1919 (Box 116, Folder 8)
      - Reestablishment of Arbitration, 1909-1912 (Box 311, Folder 43)
      - Report on Commercial Arbitration at the Commercial Law League of America, 1920 (Box 116, Folder 9)
      - Request for Articles written by Bernheimer, 1919 (Box 116, Folder 10)
      - Requests and Inquiries
        - 1922-1926 (Box 311, Folder 44)
        - 1923-1924 (Box 311, Folder 45)
      - Rose and Paskus, 1927 (Box 311, Folder 46)
      - Shishanian, John A., 1926-1927 (Box 311, Folder 47)
      - Silk Association of America, 1921-1925 (Box 116, Folder 11)
      - Snider, J.B., 1926 (Box 323, Folder 8)
      - Snow, C.D.--Foreign Commerce Department, 1921-1924 (Box 116, Folder 12)
      - Speaking Appointments, 1916-1919 (Box 116, Folder 13)
      - Standard Clause for Arbitration, 1920 (Box 116, Folder 14)
      - Starnes, George T., 1926 (Box 323, Folder 9)
      - St.Ledger, A. and Compulsory Arbitration in Australia, 1916-1920 (Box 116, Folder 15)
      - Taft, William, 1919 (Box 323, Folder 10)
      - Toulmin, H.A., 1916 (Box 116, Folder 16)
      - Tregoe, J.H., National Association of Credit Men, 1914-1917 (Box 116, Folder 17)
      - University of Chicago, 1919 (Box 116, Folder 18)
      - Uppercu Cadillac Corporation, 1923 (Box 323, Folder 11)
      - Van Amringe, Guy, 1919 (Box 116, Folder 19)
      - Walton Arbitration Law, 1920-1921 (Box 116, Folder 20)
      - Whitehouse, Davis and Company, Inc., 1926 (Box 323, Folder 12)
      - Wholesale and Retail Credit Men's Associations of Minneapolis, 1917-1919 (Box 116, Folder 21)
      - Wilkinson, Huxley, Byron and Knight, 1926 (Box 323, Folder 13)
      - Winterville High School, 1916 (Box 116, Folder 22)
      - Wood, Will R., 1921 (Box 116, Folder 23)
- Series VI: Committees, 1822-1972
  Series VI documents the activities of the Chamber’s administrative and general committees. Formed to address a specific subject or function, committees were comprised of voluntary members elected by the Chamber’s membership. Committee records contain correspondence, reports, and meeting minutes, both bound and loose.
  - Subseries VI.1: Administrative Committees, 1864-1973
    The purpose of most of the administrative committees of the Chamber of Commerce was to oversee routine functions such as lunch service, committee nominations, and Chamber membership. This subseries contains materials that document those functions; however, a large portion of the subseries is devoted to the administrative records and meeting minutes of the Executive Committee. Perhaps the most significant of the administrative committees, the Executive Committee acted as the managerial body of the Chamber. It received all general committee reports prior to their submission to the Chamber’s membership; as a result, the Executive Committee meeting minutes found in this subseries often contain these reports as well as a record of suggested actions and final resolutions. It should be noted that in some cases the bound volumes of Executive Committee minutes also contain minutes from the Chamber's general committees; these volumes are identified in the container list.
    - Admissions Committee, 1973 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee
      - General
        - 1876-1889 (Box 333, Folder 1)
        - 1909-1934 (Box 333, Folder 2)
        - 1943-1951 (Box 333, Folder 3)
        - 1966 (Box 333, Folder 4)
        - 1967 (Box 333, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence
        - 1917-1923 (Box 333, Folder 6)
        - 1921-1923 (Box 333, Folder 7)
      - Chairman, 1922-1923 (Box 333, Folder 8)
      - Hearing on Immigration, 1922-1923 (Box 333, Folder 9)
      - Memorandum of Business, 1922-1923 (Box 333, Folder 10)
      - Meeting Minutes
        - 1860-1882 (bound volume also contains minutes from other committees) (Box 484)
        - 1864-1971 (bound volume) (Box 412)
        - 1871-1882 (bound volume) (Box 413)
        - 1883-1887 (bound volume) (Box 414)
        - 1887-1898 (bound volume also contains minutes from other committees) (Box 415)
        - 1895-1896 (bound volume also contains minutes from other committees) (Box 416)
        - 1898-1910 (bound volume also contains minutes from other committees) (Box 417)
        - 1902 Sub-Executive Committee (bound volume) (Box 418)
        - 1909-1925 Financial Supplement to Meeting Minutes (bound volume) (Box 419)
        - 1910-1918 (bound volume also contains minutes from other committees) (Box 420)
        - 1918-1923 (bound volume) (Box 421)
        - 1923-1929 (bound volume) (Box 422)
        - 1929-1934 (bound volume) (Box 423)
        - 1935-1945 (bound volume) (Box 424)
        - 1945-1958 (bound volume) (Box 425)
        - 1958-1968 (bound volume) (Box 426)
        - 1968-1973 (bound volume) (Box 427)
      - Merchants Association, Joint Meeting with, 1920 (Box 333, Folder 11)
      - Monthly Meeting Business, 1922-1923 (Box 333, Folder 12)
      - National Budget System, 1916-1920 (Box 334, Folder 1)
      - Nominating Committee, 1924 (Box 334, Folder 2)
      - Report on the High Cost of Living, 1919 (Box 334, Folder 3)
      - Reports, 1916-1964 (Box 334, Folder 4)
      - Soldier Bonus, 1923 (Box 334, Folder 5)
      - Sub-Committee and Committee on Arbitration, 1922 (Box 334, Folder 6)
      - Sub-Committee on Budget, 1919-1939 (Box 334, Folder 7)
    - House Committee
      - Daily Luncheon, 1922-1923 (Box 334, Folder 8)
      - Minutes, 1921 (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - Members List--Committees, 1894-1903 (bound volume) (Box 453)
    - Nominating Committee
      - General, 1880-1923 (Box 342, Folder 2)
      - General, 1963-1964 (Box 334, Folder 10)
      - General, 1965 (Box 334, Folder 11)
  - Subseries VI.2: General Committees, 1822-1973
    The second subseries is comprised of the Chamber’s general, or standing, committees. Numerous and widely varied, these committees were formed to provide a through examination of subjects of interest to the Chamber. Joint, special, or sub-committees were often formed to address specific topics in more depth and detail. Committees represented in this subseries address subjects such as commercial education, finance and currency, shipping, trade, transportation, and urban development. Records of each committee are inconsistent; however, files often contain correspondence, meeting minutes, and reports. It should be noted that, prior to the late 19th century, all general committees were referred to by a uniform title: the Committee of the Chamber of Commerce. Records of these early committees can be found at the beginning of the subseries; the remaining committees are alphabetized by subject.
    - Chamber of Commerce, Committee of the
      - General
        - 1822-1921 (Box 279, Folder 1)
        - 1865-1920 (Box 255, Folder 1)
        - 1886-1898 (Box 255, Folder 2)
        - 1927-1935 (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - Assorted Committees, 1864-1885 (bound volume) (Box 477)
      - Assorted Committees, 1864-1886 (bound volume) (Box 481)
      - Assorted Committees, 1870-1874 (bound volume) (Box 478)
      - Assorted Committees, 1870-1886 (bound volume) (Box 483)
      - Assorted Committees, 1870-1887 (bound volume) (Box 482)
      - Assorted Committees, 1870-1887 (bound volume) (Box 485)
      - The Chinese Exclusion Act, 1889 (Box 374, Folder 10)
      - Quarantine, 1858 (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - Reports, 1868-1874 (bound volume) (Box 454)
      - Scrip Dividend of Mutual Insurance Companies, 1844 (Box 342, Folder 3)
      - Shipping Matters, 1872-1880 (Box 279, Folder 11)
      - Ship-Raising, Undated (Box 342, Folder 4)
      - U.S.S. Kearsarge, 1864-1865 (Box 257, Folder 2)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Special Committee of the--General
      - 1874 (Box 279, Folder 2)
      - 1876-1909 (Box 255, Folder 4)
      - 1877-1904 (Box 255, Folder 5)
      - 1886-1898 (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - Three, Committee of, undated (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Five, Special Committee of, 1878 (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - Five, Sub-Executive Committee of, 1902-1903 (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - Five to Examine Street Congestion, Special Committee of, 1903 (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Seven in Honor of Whitelaw Reid, Committee of, 1912 (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Sixteen on the Death of Alexander E. Orr, Committee of, undated (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Seventy to the Dock Department, Committee of, 1895-1896 (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - One Hundred, Committee of, 1919-1920 (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - 150th Anniversary of the Chamber, Special Committee on, 1916-1918 (Box 256, Folder 9)
    - Abrogation of Discriminating Rates, Special Committee for the, 1882 (Box 256, Folder 10)
    - Agriculture, Committee on, 1901 (Box 256, Folder 11)
    - Agriculture and its Problems, Committee on, 1923 (Box 256, Folder 12)
    - Agriculture and its Problems, Special Committee on, 1923 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - American Shipping, Committee on, 1881-1915 (Box 256, Folder 13)
    - Anti-Trust Legislation, Committee on, 1914 (Box 256, Folder 14)
    - Appointed to Consider the Bill Entitled "An Act to provide adequate revenue for the support…", Special Committee, 1900 (Box 256, Folder 15)
    - Arrangements for the 153rd Annual Banquet, Committee on, undated (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Arrangements for the Visit to the Navy Yard, Committee of, 1878 (Box 256, Folder 16)
    - Aviation, Special Committee on, 1943-1946 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Banking Law, Commission to Revise the, 1914 (3 Folders) (Box 279, Folder 6-8)
    - Bankruptcy Laws, Special Committee on, 1880-1885 (Box 256, Folder 17)
    - Banquet Committee, 1920-1922 (Box 279, Folder 9)
    - Building Committee, 1882-1911 (Box 256, Folder 18)